{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Tree \u0026 Shrub Maintenance Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40327/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40327,"taskName":"Trees \u0026 Shrubs - Treat, Protect and Maintain","taskDescription":"Treat, Protect and Maintain Trees \u0026 Shrubs","xmTaskDescriptor":"Tree \u0026 Shrub Maintenance Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":247,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Trees Shrubs Treat protection landscaping","textMessagingName":"Tree Protect","rolloverLongDesc":"Experts in diagnosing \u0026 treating a wide variety of problems with trees and shrubs. Also handles preventative measures such as added supports, deer fences, support cables, etc. Note separate category for lightning protection.","rolloverShortDesc":"Pests, disease, feeding, cabling, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Treat, Protect and Maintain Trees \u0026 Shrubs.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Tree Maintenance \u0026 Protection \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Treat a Diseased Tree","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":79,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Treat, Protect and Maintain Trees \u0026 Shrubs","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Trees \u0026 Shrubs - Treat, Protect and Maintain","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Tree \u0026 Shrub Project","urlName":"Trees-Shrubs-Treat-Protect-and-Maintain","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Tree Maintenance \u0026 Protection Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Trees,Shrubs,Treat,protection,landscaping,root,trunk,winter,pruning,injection,fertilization,Deep,treating,Disease,Maintain,Protect,arborist","emcCategoryOid":-12074,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":624,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40327/":{"taskOID":40327,"originalTaskOID":40327,"setID":624,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6220,"questionDisplayText":"Tree, Shrub Services Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What tree and shrub services do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8155,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and advise","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and advise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8156,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8157,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Basic maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Basic maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8158,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Deep root fertilization","answerDisplayText":"Deep root fertilization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8159,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8160,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Trunk injection applications","answerDisplayText":"Trunk injection applications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8161,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pruning","answerDisplayText":"Pruning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8162,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7182,"questionDisplayText":"# of Trees and Shrubs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many trees/shrubs are involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6220,"questionDisplayText":"Tree, Shrub Services Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What tree and shrub services do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8155,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and advise","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and advise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8156,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8157,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Basic maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Basic maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8158,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Deep root fertilization","answerDisplayText":"Deep root fertilization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8159,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8160,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Trunk injection applications","answerDisplayText":"Trunk injection applications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8161,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pruning","answerDisplayText":"Pruning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8162,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8155,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inspect and advise","answerDisplayText":"Inspect and advise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8156,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8157,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Basic maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Basic maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8158,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Deep root fertilization","answerDisplayText":"Deep root fertilization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8159,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8160,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Trunk injection applications","answerDisplayText":"Trunk injection applications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8161,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Pruning","answerDisplayText":"Pruning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8162,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Winter protection","answerDisplayText":"Winter protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7182,"questionDisplayText":"# of Trees and Shrubs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many trees/shrubs are involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}